# Adolfo Ramírez de Sancristóbal

# Frontend Developer

4622550422

Guanajuato, Guanajuato

in Adolfo Ramírez

Adolf97

## **Profile**

I have a degree in international trade, but 4 years ago, I discovered my passion for web development and software development with Javascript, Python, PHP and SQL. Also, since a year ago, I found my love for data science with Python.

### **Professional Experience**

2023 – present Web Developer / Frontend Developer

Guanajuato, Mexico UpVent Technologies 🗷

• Frontend Developer for different projects of the organization.

2021/08 – 2023/05 Sales Engineer

Querétaro, México RDQ, SA de CV ☑

• Creating new relationships with customers and suppliers.

• Finding and carrying out high-impact projects in industrial companies.

• Frontend developer for the current website of the company.

2019 – 2020 Web Developer / Frontend Developer

Guanajuato, México Freeland

• Frontend developer for the website of "Hotel Mesón de Juan Valle", in Guanajuato.

• Frontend developer for the website of the "Parroquia de Nuestra Señora del Patrocinio", in Guanajuato.

### **Skills**

html / CSS 4 years	••••	<b>javascript</b> 3 years	••••
<b>Typescript</b> 1 year	••••	<b>Python</b> 1 year	••••
PHP 1 year	••••	<b>SQL</b> 1 year	••••
Node.js 2 years	••••	React (NextJS) / Svelte 1 year	••••
<b>Flask</b> 1 year	••••	Git/Github 3 years	••••
Laravel	• • • • •		

#### Education

1 year

2017/08 - 2022/06 Bachelor's degree - International Trade

Guanajuato, Mexico Universidad de Guanajuato ♂

I learned about the legal processes that are necessary for goods to enter or leave the country.

The second secon

2020/10 - 2020/11 Virtual Exchange - Cultural exchange

Osaka, Japan University of Setsunan

I learned interesting aspects about Japanese culture.

2021/02 - 2021/12 Virtual - "Digital Transformation Advisor"

Guanajuato, México Alibaba Business School 🖸

I participated in Alibaba's GDT Digital Transformation course; where I was trained to support small

and medium-sized companies that want to start their own e-commerce.

Languages

EnglishJapaneseTOEFL ITP, 560 pointsJLPT, N4

**Awards** 

2019 First Place ☑

"Primer Hackathon de Dolores Hidalgo"

2019 Third Place

"BeeHack2019: Cuidado del medio ambiente"

Winner 2018

HackDay: Universidad de Guanajuato